Yes, we get superpowers!
Superpowers!
There's a monster deep within your dreams.
Taking aim for your
heart so it would seem.
Stand tall and read, go to
hell and jump for paradise.
Every time dangerous, dangerous.
We like it serious, serious, oh.
Looking deep in the dream
there is the one in pain.
Turns out that's the one who
means the most to you today.
Adventure calls now, let's go.
The balls filled between
us, they will show.
Still what we don't know.
Yes, working hard together.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Got to dream despite the rivalry.
Gotta see it through believing in you.
There's even charm in failure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
All the love and the tears
in the world we're in.
United gently bringing up
our thought again, yeah.
With the foolish ones
we love, we'll carry on.
Till we see the light, the sun will rise.
The greatest fight at its core.
Is against myself forevermore.
Come on, let's do it now, let's go.
The bonds built between
us, they will show.
So what we don't know, that's
what we call adventure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Got to dream despite the rivalry.
Gotta see it through believing in you.
There's even charm in failure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Superpowers.
Yes, we're the superpowers.
It's no wonder you're frustrated.
Every time you try to take
a stand, I knock you down.
Did you notice when you
tried to throw a left punch?
I targeted your left shoulder.
And when you tried to throw a right punch.
I targeted your right shoulder, all
of your efforts have been in vain;
you are nothing but a fool
drowning in your own failure.
This is what it's like when your
enemy can predict your every move.
Forcing you to lash out in
desperation is just the appetizer.
Whether you throw a left
kick or a right kick,
I will strike you before
you can even make contact.
And I won't let up until I
see your heart burst in two.
There's intent behind every attack.
A hint, too.
Don't attack your foe blindly.
Focus.
Die!
It's as I suspected.
It's infrequent, but he's able
to see the future, same as me.
Son of a biscuit!
What's wrong?
I screwed up big time!
It totally slipped my mind,
but I was supposed to pipe roses of
whipped cream on the top of the cake!
Let me take care of it.
Pastry bag, please? Yes, sir!
Skywalk!
So cool! It's wonderful!
Bam! It's ready.
Wow! Nice work!
It's finally complete.
The ultimate wedding cake masterpiece.
So how's it look? Yeah!
Incredible, Lili!
Smells so good I could paint!
Agreed, dammit!
It came out great!
This cake don't even need to
be full of poison after all.
That big broad's gonna drop
after one bite. Arrivederci!
The cake's all done.
Made it just in time. You okay?
What happened?
You feeling all right?
Why are they all collapsing suddenly?
They really must have
worked their asses off.
Don't bother getting up.
We already know all about your plan.
Kaku Island, 1am, right?
Not that it matters.
Your friends won't even get
the chance to reach the island.
Soon they'll be met by my brother's fleets
waiting in anticipation of their arrival.
And the same fate is in store for you,
should you manage to escape somehow.
Doesn't matter.
Hmm?
I'm still gonna make it out
of here, one way or another.
You sound confident, like
it's destined to happen.
By the way, Pudding and Chiffon, couldn't
have done it without you. Thanks a ton.
Seriously, with this cake, I'll
definitely save my friends.
There's no way you know that for sure!
Yeah, the cake is finished
and all, but big whoop!
I hate to tell ya, but
they might be dead already!
Besides, he even knows if Mama
will like the cake or not.
Honestly,
this seems like a big
waste of time bringing
this Serious excuse of
a cake to your Sanji.
Tell him you didn't mean it pudding.
Oh.
Whatever the case is it's
too late to worry now!
You can't run away!
I want my wedding cape! Now! Let's rumble!
Time for monster point!
I'll make sure she doesn't come back.
What the hell? A monster?
They have monsters?
Since when?
Napoleon, are you prepared? Extend!
Hey, Chopper!
Everyone, listen up!
Buy us as much time as possible!
Sure.
Sounds like a plan.
We're always right here beside you.
Until that moment arrives, we will
endure whatever she can heave our way.
Big Mom doesn't know it's coming her way.
The greatest cake ever made.
I swear I will beat you.
Then I'll go and rejoin my crew.
Because my friends believe in me.
I'll slice you in two!
No!
It's time to use Ghost Sword!
Oh, please!
I'm not here!
Get out!
Chopper! Stop! You're hurt!
Don't worry, I'm okay.
Big Mom, do your worst.
I can at least drag you into the
murky waters with me before I go down.
You're a fiery one, aren't you?
Let's see if this is still a good on
that threat after you witness this.
Oh, no.
But how?
At that size, no amount
of seawater will help.
They're so, so fiercely. Unreal.
Let's see how far you guys can run now.
We can't stick around, or we'll
burn up alongside the summit.
It's a shame, since we've
managed to make it this far.
Not to mention, Sanji
will be here any minute.
It's been fun, you guys.
Really?
Now, where's my cake?
Wow, where is that coming from?
Stop getting up.
How do you expect to win?
His observation Haki is nearly
sharp enough to compete with my own.
If I don't put an end to him soon,
the unthinkable could happen.
It's them!
They're here!
It's their ship!
You see that?
It's the cake!
Sancti's crew really pulled through!
They brought it!
The lights, Sancti! Sancti!
Mama?
Is that...
Goodness, that smells good!
Hey, Blackleg, looks like
we got eyes on your ship.
Stinking Prometheus, look
how freaking huge you got.
Powered up by Big Mom's soul.
Hate to say it, but look
who he's toting around.
That's Big Mom up there.
Father, there's a fleet, too.
I can spot Patty Sparrow and Bob O 'Wall.
Plus Smoothie and her crew, too. I see.
No matter how you look at
it, that spells trouble.
Seems like the Straw Hat
ships in rough shape, though.
All right. Ready, boys? Yeah!
Remember, this is Big Mom.
You can't fool around with her. Capisce?
You plug that dame full of lead.
Then light her up.
Gee.
Oh, Mommy!
I've come to save you!
Tang.
Look, Blacklick.
Seems like your crew's been
running from Big Mom all day.
Wow, you really hung in there.
Your captain ain't even with them.
Mom!
There's a Noodle Man on board.
He's releasing some weird power.
I doubt that's Haki.
But why are they arriving
on Benji's ship, though?
I think someone's dancing on the bow.
Who cares about that?
What really matters is the cake.
I'll be damned.
They managed to recreate the wedding cake
down to every last
lickety-dollop and detail.
Hope it passes the taste test.
Nothing else can stop Mama's madness.
Although,
Buggy is standing right there.
That cake is bound to be poisoned.
What should I do?
Thanks to the smell she backed
off, I really got lucky.
Man, I thought I was a gunner for sure.
Should we attempt to destroy
the replacement wedding cake?
No, if we do that,
then there will be no stopping Mama from
lickety-liquidating
Toto Land as we know it.
But if the cake is poisoned,
then both the country and the pirate
operation will crumble without her.
What should I do?
This is a lickety-lose-lose situation.
Hey Black Leg, you got yourself a deal,
Paulie, and don't worry—we'll
step aside, promise.
We
can handle the cake from here and there;
won't be any aggression
till that bird has a fill.
But
I'm free to do as I please afterwards,
yeah, that's correct—I only had one job:
the wedding cake—bake a new
one to calm big mom down.
Okay, let's do it all
right—we're ready, Sanji.
Coming then—hurry, the hell
up, unless you want to die!
Hey pudding—take it easy.
die hey pudding
take it easy
Thanks. You good?
For sure.
See you soon.
Chip on.
Robin!
We'd better make this fast!
Listen closely!
Go quickly enough that
neither of my brothers notice!
Roger!
Would that be my wedding cake?
It's there!
I knew it had to be around! Quickly!
Yeah!
Mama!
I can't see my cake!
Here she comes!
Turn Starboy! Yes, sir!
Go southwest at full speed!
Head toward Lock Island!
What the hell?!
Hey, Press, look!
The ship with the cake has
suddenly changed course!
Why?!
I think they're enticing Mama to
follow Bezzy's ship for some reason!
That's interesting.
Lickety-leading Mama away, are they?
Could it be that they are trying to
divide us by forcing us to split up?
Clever.
Yo-ho!
Hey there, you miss me?
Sanji! It's Sanji!
I'm putting too! Sanji!
We were barely hanging on by a thread.
I thought we were done for.
I'm so glad you're safe.
Mama Bloom!
I love you too, Nami, my sweet honey pie.
By the way, Sanji, why
were you on Veggie's ship?
Oh, yeah, long story.
Where precisely is this ship headed?
Nobody exactly knows what Big Mom will
do after she finishes eating the cake.
So Buggy and his men are luring her to
the closest island just to be safe. Huh?
Why would he willingly
volunteer to be bait?
What could he be getting out of this?
Well, he hasn't given
up on murdering her yet.
Typical.
Sounds like him.
Sonny's safety is the only
thing that matters to me.
If he can keep Big Mom away from
it, then I can't ask for more.
Do you get me?
Just look, poor Sonny.
I'm sorry that I failed to protect it.
You can't say that!
We would have been lost
without you, Jinbei!
Take it back!
We can catch up later.
I'm just relieved you're all safe.
Anyway, what are Pedro and
Karen up to at the moment?
Well?
Oh, uh, they're in the cabin.
Uh, and they're both wiped
out from all the fighting.
Press, what should we do?
What do we chase?
Brahat or Mama?
We can't let him lickety
leave with his life.
Bada-bada-bada-bada-bada.
Hey, Press, it's me, Veggie.
Veggie, you backstabber!
What are you up to?
Why the hell are you the one
lickety-lugging that cake around?
Don't you worry about that.
I'll be dealing with Mama's hunger pains.
I'll let her have her fill the cake until
she calms down. You rat! Liar! Traitor!
What did you put in the cake?
You messed with it, didn't you?
I assure you there's
nothing wrong with it.
Besides, Puddin had a
hand in making the thing.
If that's the case, then tell
me where she is right now!
I wouldn't worry about
the details if I was you.
Maybe you should focus on
taking care of Straw Hat.
I got things down pat on my head, eh?
What are you, son of a...
Calvick!
Fiji! Hello!
We're going after that
bastard, Bavawa! Huh?
I'm 100 % positive he's plotting to
go through with the assassination!
It's lickety-likely he's done
something to pudding as well.
Do you think so, Pedos?
Maybe we should follow Straw Hat's ship.
It will sink a cacao island anyway.
And besides,
did you forget that we
have a certain someone
who we can count on to finish the mission?
Huh? Oh, yeah.
Why won't you pick up?
Hey, Smoothie,
I need to know if you're still a part
of the fleet trailing the Straw Hats.
Yeah, right on your tail, Pedos.
I need you to stick to the Straw Hats
like your lickety-life depends on it.
Boboar and I are going
after Buggy and Mama.
Squeeze every last drop of lickety life
from those rotten little trespassers.
Don't stop tormenting them until
they jump off the edge of sanity!
Do I make myself clear?
Abundantly so.
Perlick: If that's what he wanted, then he
should have just asked me from the start.
Our poor brother, Press.
Getting distracted, isn't he?
We should have stayed put on Cacao Island.
I was really enjoying all
the tea and chocolate.
He's just being impatient.
These men are such idiots.
No time for complaining.
All right, let's prepare for battle.
We're going to sink Straw Hat's ship.
We shall stop them before
they reach Kaku Island. Yeah!
Hmm.
Mm-hmm.
They know it all?
Even where we're meeting Luffy?
Yeah, I bet Kaku Island's
surrounded with ships by now.
Damn.
It appears that they are treating us as
a true threat, which is unusual for them.
This will be our final obstacle,
but likely our biggest as well.
We're gonna rescue Luffy no matter
what and then make a break for it.
However,
we'll have to avoid their fleets at all
costs or else we're gonna be done for.
You look pathetic.
Your foot slipped, you amateur.
Straw Hat!
Oh, my plan is working!
Big bra!
Did you know that I was helping all along?
I hadn't realized that. Thank you.
What a good girl you are.
Flampe, you truly are my favorite sister.
Oh, man, I miss Clippers. I am cute.
Just one moment of recklessness.
That's what can decide a battle.
Never let your guard down.
Don't see another one!
What's the matter, Straw Hat?
Just when I was starting
to admit you were worth it.
What a disappointment!
Did I imagine that?
I swear I saw it!
Imagination is part of it.
Beyond such tricks of the mind,
you will find observation, Haki.
Basically, it's something you
learn to feel out subconsciously.
Subconsciously?
He's stood up?
He's looking pretty shaky, though.
Fine, one more I'll do it.
This time I'll nail you with a numbing
needle ten times more potent than the last.
This will show you for
wasting my brother's time.
Drop dead, you dirty little ape.
Numbin' Needle!
What?!
My Needle was totally silent!
How in the heck did he dodge?!
The moron fell down anyway!
Keep it down.
They're gonna notice us.
But I can't help it.
Just look at him.
Tramble like a newborn mom.
It's such a pathetic sight.
Wabble wabble.
Knock it off.
The kid's so laughing.
Hey, look, look, look.
He can't figure it out.
He's drenched in blood and stumbling
around, but he doesn't know what hit him.
That moron.
His determination is
almost too much to stomach.
Throw in the towel already.
Slumpay.
Dammit.
Whee!
I think Big Brown might
be looking right at me!
He's so cool, I just want to screw you!
Don't get freaked out, but I
think he's coming this way.
Really?
Well done.
You're such a splendid
little sister, Flampe.
Good girl.
He's going to freeze me.
The day has finally come.
I am so not ready.
I see now.
So it was you, Flampe.
By using that blowgun you love so
much, you took away his mobility.
During our heated standoff, your
interference caused his focus to falter.
I knew something felt off.
That was when I landed the blow that
ripped a bloody hole in his torso.
Do you really think that I'd want to
claim victory in such a dishonorable way?
Are you seeing this crap, Lady Flumpe?
The wounded animal's getting back up.
Hey, that made me laugh.
It's trembling.
Little baby deer walking for his body.
Yeah, I can't wait to see General
Katakuri beat the crap out of this idiot!
Obviously!
It'll be another flawless victory!
Kick his butt, big bro!
Flop.
It was you, wasn't it?
That's right!
It was me!
I did it all for you!
Aren't I just the cutest,
sweetest, and most considerate
out of all of your little sisters?
No one in the world is more perfect than
you and I get to be your save! Lucky me!
I'll collect those haircuts now, please!
Big bro!
You idiots!
What's so funny?
What did you do that for?
What the hell?
I shouldn't have to tell you this.
When a man goes to battle,
don't patronize him!
Are you worried about that?
Ow!
I love you, gold man!
If you laugh at a man fighting for his
life, then why not have a laugh at me, too?
You suck!
Agreed!
What a bummer!
Ew!
That's your blood!
Why are you so gross?
Where'd you put the calm, cool, and
collected big bro that I love and admire?
What the hell has gotten into you, huh?
Why would you stab yourself?
You big lame ass!
You are totally not the same
cut of curry that I know!
Totally pathetic!
You pelican eel looking bastard!
That is what he looks like!
Stop it, Lady Pompey! I'm gonna...
I'm gonna pee my pants!
So gross!
You really let me down!
Here comes a pelican eel! Stay away!
That kid's a monster!
Don't let him get you!
Hey, aren't you gonna say something?
Hurry up and take some pictures!
We gotta get the word out.
Everyone needs to see
this messed up space!
Come on!
What's the rush?
Well, you might hold
it still for a second.
General Katakuri, can you
look over here real quick?
That chum for me does
look like a pelican eel!
The flawless big brother I once had
is dead to me now. You hear that?
Die, Charlotte Katakuri!
I'll send these photos
of your freaky face to
every fan club never in
every island in Totoland!
How dare you splutter
your grimy blood on me!
That's the price you pay for
snubbing your favorite little sister!
I can't believe I
thought you were perfect!
You're so disgusting!
I'm ashamed to admit
that I'm related to you!
You're both gonna get it,
and don't think I forgot how you
ruined the tea party, Straw Hat!
Just looking at your dumb
faces is annoying me!
I'm aiming straight for
the heart this time!
I hope you enjoy venomous needles!
What have happened?!
I'll never forgive you!
I won't let you walk away from this!
I've had enough of everyone's commentary.
They won't be able to
stand after this anyway.
Conqueror's monkey, pet monkey
can use it too, but it is a jump!